# Joanathon Zinninger

#### **UI/UX Designer**

UI designer with experience in supervising office operations and customer relations. Design skills centered on producing beautiful, easy to use products that satisfy customers' needs. Empathy and determination serve as a driving force for handling any challenge.

## **Experience**

#### Illinois Department of Employment Security (2020 - 2021)

#### Fraud Specialist

 Worked on a fraud team which involved analysis, data entry, and document indexing, resulting in thousands of applications/cases being processed in a short period of time.

#### **Topline HVAC Inc. (2018 - 2020)**

Office Administration & Customer Service

- Analyzed work fluctuation trends to create new employee schedules and effectively manage payroll hours, creating a better work/life balance for all and leaving employees satisfied.
- Created a new accounts receivable system to resolve issues with money monitoring, resulting in accurate organization and no more unaccounted funds.
- Ensured efficient project operations by making sure all equipment, products, and materials were in stock, scheduling the proper technicians/teams, and collecting needed payments.
- Ensuring customers received top-quality service and were left happy and satisfied through over-the-phone and in person interactions.
- Scheduled and organized provided services in a timely fashion to satisfy customer needs and expedite technician workflow.

#### Panera Bread (2016 - 2018)

#### Customer Service

- Contributed to a warm and inviting atmosphere by greeting and assisting all customers in a friendly manner, leaving them happy creating return customers.
- Crafted numerous picture-worthy drinks with accuracy and speed even during busy hours and ensured fast service and satisfied customers.

## **Contact**

joanathonz@gmail.com

(708) 514-9129

portfolio.com

in linkedin.com/in/joanathonz

### **Skills**

User Interface Design

User Research

**User Flows** 

Prototyping

Wireframing

**Usability Testing** 

Styles Guides

Branding

Illustration

**Public Speaking** 

## **Tools**

Sketch

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Microsoft Office

Google Worspace

## **Education**

Careerfoundry
UI Immersion (2021)

Elmwood Park
High School (2018)